ilovemyfreedom.org 2019-06-30

# Privacy Policy

Privacy policy for ilovemyfreedom.org, trumpcollectorcoins.com, AmericaFirstPolls.com

Last updated on June 20, 2019

We know that you care how your information is used, and we appreciate your trust that we will use it carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our Privacy Policy.

By visiting us, you are accepting the privacy policy described below.

 **WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**

Information you provide. We receive and store information you enter. For example, when you search for or buy a product or service, or when you supply information such as your address, phone number or credit card. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of some of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our website, and communicating with you. In addition, if you choose, we may share your information with other companies who provide goods or services that you are interested in. Please see the “opt-in/opt-out” section of this Policy.

Like many websites, we use “cookies”. Cookies are small programs that we transfer to your hard drive that allow us to recognize you and to provide you with a customized shopping experience. If you do not want us to use cookies, you can easily disable them by going to the toolbar of your web browser, and clicking on the “help” button. Follow the instructions that will prevent the browser from accepting cookies, or set the browser to inform you when you receive a new cookie. In addition, you may visit this and other websites anonymously through the use of utilities provided by other private companies.

Other information. Every computer has an ip (internet protocol) address. Ip addresses of computers used to visit this site are noted. In addition, we automatically collect other information such as email addresses, browser types, operating systems, and the url addresses of sites clicked to and from this site.

Information from other sources. We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. This may include updated delivery and address information from our shippers or other sources so that we can correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily.

 **THIRD PARTY SITES**

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily make your personal information available for viewing by third parties online – for example on message boards, web logs, through email, or in chat areas – that information can be seen, collected and used by others besides us. We cannot be responsible for any unauthorized third-party use of such information.

Some of our third-party advertisers and ad servers that place and present advertising on the site also may collect information from you via cookies, web beacons or similar technologies. These third-party advertisers and ad servers may use the information they collect to help present their advertisements, to help measure and research the advertisements’ effectiveness, or for other purposes. The use and collection of your information by these third-party advertisers and ad servers is governed by the relevant third-party’s privacy policy and is not covered by our privacy policy. Indeed, the privacy policies of these third-party advertisers and ad servers may be different from ours. If you have any concerns about a third party’s use of cookies or web beacons or use of your information, you should visit that party’s website and review its privacy policy.

The site also includes links to other websites and provides access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies we do not control. When you access another website or purchase third-party products or services through the site, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting or the provider of such products or services.

 **HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?**

Customized shopping. We use your information to better serve you by providing a customized shopping experience. As noted above, you may “opt-out” of this customization, or even visit and shop anonymously.

We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, and processing credit card payments. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.  
Special offers. We may send you special offers from time to time, unless you choose to “opt-out” of receiving such offers. In addition, we may also send you special offers from other companies. Again, you may “opt-out”. If we send you offers from other businesses, we do not share your personal information with them. The offers come directly through us. Please see the “opt-in/opt-out” selection at the end of this policy.  
Business transfers. As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores or assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that we are acquired, customer information will be one of the transferred assets.  
Law enforcement.

If we receive a lawful court order to release account or other personal information then we will comply with the law. We will also release information when necessary to protect the life, safety or property of others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk.

 **YOUR CHOICE: OPT-IN OR OPT-OUT.**

It is your choice whether to receive emails or special offers from us or others. The following section provides you with this choice. Please note the default settings.  
Please send me email or other mail informing me of special offers of your products or services.  
Please do not send me email or other mail informing me of special offers of your products or services.  
Please send me email or other mail informing me of special offers of related products or services from other companies.  
please do not send me email or other mail informing me of special offers of related products or services from other companies.

 **GOOGLE ANALYTICS**

We also use Google Analytics advertiser features to optimize our business. Advertiser features include:  
Remarketing with google analytics  
Google display network impression reporting  
Doubleclick platform integrations  
Google analytics demographics and interest reporting

By enabling these google analytics display features, we are required to notify our visitors by disclosing the use of these features and that we and third-party vendors use first-party cookies (such as the google analytics cookie) or other first-party identifiers, and third-party cookies (such as the doubleclick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to gather data about your activities on our site. Among other uses, this allows us to contact you if you begin to fill out our check-out form but abandon it before completion with an email reminding you to complete your order. The “remarketing” feature allows us to reach people who previously visited our site, and match the right audience with the right advertising message.

You can opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting google’s ad settings and/or you may opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the network advertising initiative opt-out page  
.  
**FACEBOOK**

As advertisers on Facebook and through our Facebook page, we, (not Facebook) may collect content or information from a Facebook user and such information may be used in the same manner specified in this privacy policy. You consent to our collection of such information.  
We abide by Facebook’s data use restrictions.

Any ad data collected, received or derived from our Facebook ad (“Facebook advertising data”) is only shared with someone acting on our behalf, such as our service provider. We are responsible for ensuring that our service providers protect any Facebook advertising data or any other information obtained from us, limit our use of all of that information, and keep it confidential and secure.

We do not use Facebook advertising data for any purpose (including retargeting, commingling data across multiple advertisers’ campaigns, or allowing piggybacking or redirecting with tags), except on an aggregate and anonymous basis (unless authorized by Facebook) and only to assess the performance and effectiveness of our Facebook advertising campaigns.

We do not use Facebook advertising data, including the targeting criteria for a facebook ad, to build, append to, edit, influence, or augment user profiles, including profiles associated with any mobile device identifier or other unique identifier that identifies any particular user, browser, computer or device.

We do not transfer any Facebook advertising data (including anonymous, aggregate, or derived data) to any ad network, ad exchange, data broker or other advertising or monetization related service.

 **GENERAL DATA PRIVACY REGULATION (GDPR)**

The GDPR took effect on May 25, 2018, and is intended to protect the data of European Union (EU) citizens.

As a company that markets its site, content, products and/or services online we do not specifically target our marketing to the eu or conduct business in or to the eu in any meaningful way. If the data that you provide to us in the course of your use of our site, content, products and/or services is governed by gdpr, we will abide by the relevant portions of the regulation.

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), or are accessing this site from within the eea, you may have the right to request: access to, correction of, deletion of; portability of; and restriction or objection to processing, of your personal data, from us. This includes the “right to be forgotten.”

To make any of these requests, please contact our gdpr contact at GDPR@_______.COM

 **CHILDREN’S PRIVACY STATEMENT  
**  
This children’s privacy statement explains our practices with respect to the online collection and use of personal information from children under the age of thirteen, and provides important information regarding their rights under federal law with respect to such information.  
This site is not directed to children under the age of thirteen and we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the site. We screen users who wish to provide personal information in order to prevent users under the age of thirteen from providing such information. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from a user under the age of thirteen as part of the site, we will delete such information from our records. If we change our practices in the future, we will obtain prior, verifiable parental consent before collecting any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the site.

Because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the site, we also do not knowingly distribute such information to third parties.

We do not knowingly allow children under the age of thirteen to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information through the site.  
Because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the site, we do not condition the participation of a child under thirteen in the site’s online activities on providing personally identifiable information.

 **HOW DO WE STORE YOUR INFORMATION?**

Your information is stored at the list server that delivers the Site content and messaging. Your information can only be accessed by those who help manage those lists in order to deliver e-mail to those who would like to receive the Site material.

All of the messaging or emails that are sent to you by the Site include an unsubscribe link in them. You can remove yourself at any time from our mailing list by clicking on the unsubscribe link that can be found in every communicaiton that we send you.

 **CONTACT US**

If you would like to learn more about our privacy policy, or to access your personally identifiable information contained on our website, you may contact us for assistance at our support desk.no portion of this website can be copied without written permission from the author.

 **DISCLAIMER**

This policy may be changed at any time at our discretion. If we should update this policy, we will post the updates to this page on our website.

Making Web, LLC and DBA I Love My Freedom™ and associates are not affiliated with or sponsored by Donald J. Trump for President, Inc. (campaign).
